https://www.bollywoodhungama.com/privacy/

Skip to contentBollywood Entertainment at its bestLast Updated 11.12.2020 | 11:23 AM IST SEARCHLANGUAGEFOLLOW US ON
FEEDBACK
Xtrending Sushant Singh Rajput Coolie No.1 Ludo Bellbottom Sooryavanshi Laxmmi
NewsBollywood NewsFeaturesSlideshowsSouth CinemaInternationalTelevisionOTT / Web SeriesFashion & LifestyleMoviesUpcoming ReleasesTop 100 MoviesMovie ReviewsCelebsTop 100 CelebsPhotosParties and EventsCeleb PhotosCeleb WallpapersMovie StillsFirst LookMovie WallpapersToonsMusicSong LyricsMusic ReviewsVideosTrailersCeleb InterviewsFirst Day First ShowParties & EventsBollywood This WeekExclusive & SpecialsMovie SongsBox OfficeBox Office CollectionAnalysis & FeaturesAll Time Top GrossersOverseas Box Office100 Crore club200 Crore clubTop Male CelebsTop Female CelebsTrendingCoronavirusBharti SinghBigg Boss 14Sushant Singh News Bollywood Entertainment at its bestLast Updated 11.12.2020 | 11:23 AM IST
feedback
language
follow us on
Bollywood Hungama
»
Privacy Policy
Bollywood Hungama has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site, mobile site, application which includes the Bollywood Hungama Windows Application as well as the app on Google Play Store and iOS.Information Automatically LoggedWe use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. Your IP address or demographic information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.CookiesVarious methods are employed to gather this data. “Cookies” are used to distinguish and relate non personal data to individuals. These are “small strings of text” that are stored in browsers; cookies are not programs that can damage your computer. If you wish to stop the cookie functionality on your browser, you may do so.Our Site uses cookies to make sure you don’t see the same ad repeatedly. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, and to save your login information so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. Information collected using cookies is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.AdvertisersWe work with various third party advertising networks. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by advertising network, and we do not have access to this information.Registration FormsBollywood Hungama does not collect personally identifiable information about individuals, except when individuals provide such information on a voluntary basis during registration.Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary as well as dissemination of prizes. Contact information is never shared with anyone or disclosed to third parties.The Demographic information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. We use this data to tailor our visitor’s experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. This data is also used to serve banner ads.External LinksThis site contains links to other sites. Bollywood Hungama is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.Public ForumsThis site makes chat rooms, opinion polls, and/or news available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.SecurityThis site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We make every effort to maintain quality of service and prevent misuse.Children’s Guidelines ( Children under 13 )This site collects and uses personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. This site allows children to post or distribute any personally identifiable information without first obtaining verifiable parental consent.Contacting the Web SiteIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us.You hereby confirm that you shall abide to these Terms & Conditions and shall also abide to all the applicable laws of the land.Content on this website may occasionally contain strong language (which may be unsuitable for children), unusual humor (which may be unsuitable for adults), nudity, violence, and imitable behavior etc. Viewers are requested to exercise discretion when listening to and / or viewing such content.
Bollywood directoryMoviesCelebrities
998A
837B
441C
750D
202E
157F
412G
218Z
3# New Bollywood Movies Durgamati: The Myth MovieTorbaaz MovieIndoo Ki Jawani MovieThe Last Color MovieSayonee MovieShakeela MovieCoolie No.1 MovieMere Desh Ki Dharti MovieLooop Lapeta MovieGaalib Movie
Bollywood Movie Reviews Tenet Review Suraj Pe Mangal Bhari Review Chhalaang Review Ludo Review Laxmii Review Taish Review Ginny Weds Sunny Review Khaali Peeli Review Dolly Kitty Aur Woh Chamakte Sitare Review Sadak 2 Review
Public Movie Reviews Angrezi Medium Public Review Baaghi 3 Public Review Thappad Public Review Shubh Mangal Zyada Saavdhan Public Review BHOOT: Part One – The Haunted Ship Public Review Love Aaj Kal Public Review Shikara Public Review Malang Public Review Jawaani Jaaneman Public Review Panga Public Review
Box Office Collection
Fastey Fasaatey Box Office Suraj Pe Mangal Bhari Box Office Angrezi Medium Box Office Bloodshot (English) Box Office Careless Box Office Baaghi 3 Box Office Most Common Budbak Box Office Kaamyaab Box Office Onward (English) Box Office Sonic The Hedgehog (English) Box Office Top Celebs Ajay DevgnKajolSaif Ali KhanShraddha KapoorTiger ShroffVarun DhawanAyushmann KhurranaAditya Roy KapurDisha PataniKartik AaryanDeepika PadukoneTaapsee Pannu Bollywood Box Office
Box Office Collection Analysis & Features All Time Top Grossers Overseas Box Office 100 Crore club 200 Crore club Top Actors Top Actress Box Office Collection 2019 Box Office Collection 2018 Box Office Collection 2017 Latest Bollywood News
Bollywood News Featured Movie News Latest Box Office News Box Office Updates Box Office Business Talk Box Office Overseas News Latest News Slideshows #BollywoodNews #BollywoodNewsToday #BollywoodNewsHindi Top Bollywood Photos
Parties and Events Latest Celeb Photos Celeb Wallpapers Movie Stills First Look Movie Wallpapers Toons New Latest Videos
Top Movie Video Songs Celebrity Interview Videos Movie Trailer Videos Party & Event Videos Exclusives & Specials Bollywood Movie Trailer THE LAST COLOR - TrailerShakeela - Teaser | Richa Chadda | Pankaj TripathiIndoo Ki Jawani Official Trailer | Kiara AdvaniGamanam: Trailer | Shriya Saran | Ilaiyaraaja |…Ganapath: Motion Poster | Tiger ShroffIt’s My Life | Nana Patekar | Harman Baweja |… Useful links
Latest Hindi News Latest Bhojpuri News Celebs@twitter Hungama.com Artist Aloud Sitemap Movie Reviews Music Reviews Bharat Official Trailer Downloads Photos
Download Celeb Photos Download Celeb Wallpapers Download Movie photos Download Celebrity Party Photos Download Movie First Look Poster Download Magazine Cover Download Movie On Set Photos Download Movie Wallpapers Home | Advertise | Privacy Policy | Feedback | Contact UsDownload App on
Copyright © 2020 Hungama Digital Media Entertainment Pvt. Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
Your Rating Click to rate on scale of 1-5 Review Title
Your Review5000 characters remaining
New notification
